{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 52,
                "_id": "03-01",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "FLSEs must provide documentation and evidence of risk-reduction activities being performed in order to:",
                "refPage": "66",
                "possible0": "develop new educational presentations.",
                "possible1": "be evaluated by an accreditation agency.",
                "possible2": "receive a continuation or increase in funding or staffing.",
                "possible3": "integrate programs outside of their authority having jurisdiction.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "_id": "03-02",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "The development or adoption of specific documentation forms and formats for documenting fire and life safety education activities is the responsibility of the:",
                "refPage": "67",
                "possible0": "shift supervisors.",
                "possible1": "administration office.",
                "possible2": "Fire and Life Safety Educator I.",
                "possible3": "authority having jurisdiction (AHJ).",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "_id": "03-03",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "One way of educating leadership is through the documentation of daily activities, specifically the _____ required to perform the job effectively and efficiently.",
                "refPage": "68",
                "possible0": "time",
                "possible1": "research",
                "possible2": "financial resources",
                "possible3": "number of meetings",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "_id": "03-04",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "A series of lessons or presentations which are designed to reach an educational goal is referred to as:",
                "refPage": "69",
                "possible0": "curriculum.",
                "possible1": "lesson plan.",
                "possible2": "presentation.",
                "possible3": "documentation.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "_id": "03-05",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "Documentation of a fire and life safety educational activity begins with the:",
                "refPage": "69",
                "possible0": "confirmation of the topic.",
                "possible1": "scheduling of the presentation.",
                "possible2": "determining the age of the target audience.",
                "possible3": "requesting of resources for the presentation.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "_id": "03-06",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "An annual activity report for a fire and emergency services agency is important, because decisions concerning _____ are based upon the information presented in it.",
                "refPage": "69",
                "possible0": "integration",
                "possible1": "sponsorships",
                "possible2": "budgeting and personnel",
                "possible3": "the number of individuals to be contacted",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "_id": "03-07",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "Which statement BEST describes a monthly activity report?",
                "refPage": "70",
                "possible0": "An FLSE I must be able to independently prepare a monthly report for the division.",
                "possible1": "A separate monthly report must be generated for each category of fire and life safety activity.",
                "possible2": "By law, monthly reports must be publicly available on the department's website or as a hard copy.",
                "possible3": "An FLSE I may not be responsible for preparing a monthly report, but needs to understand the information contained in it.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "_id": "03-08",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "Once a community is aware of the fire and life safety activities being conducted by the fire department, a critical element for the FLSE I is the importance of creating and managing a(an):",
                "refPage": "72",
                "possible0": "support staff.",
                "possible1": "work schedule.",
                "possible2": "mission statement.",
                "possible3": "organization priority.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "_id": "03-09",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "A supervisor's _____ that need to be understood and considered will be factors in the establishment of a work schedule.",
                "refPage": "72",
                "possible0": "mission",
                "possible1": "demands",
                "possible2": "background",
                "possible3": "expectations",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "_id": "03-10",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "Performing the everyday duties of a FLSE can include a time-consuming set of tasks such as:",
                "refPage": "72",
                "possible0": "mission and vision statement creation.",
                "possible1": "staying current with staff certifications.",
                "possible2": "special needs of audience or facility arrangements.",
                "possible3": "time for telephone calls and responding to e-mails.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "_id": "03-11",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "As risk-reduction activities of the fire and emergency services department become visible and noticeable in the community, it is imperative that educators:",
                "refPage": "74",
                "possible0": "not attempt to fill every request.",
                "possible1": "double-book events in case of cancellations.",
                "possible2": "refer staff members to scheduling programs.",
                "possible3": "focus on activities where there will be the least impact.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "_id": "03-12",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "An FLSE should have a comprehensive list of community resources to assist the public with:",
                "refPage": "76",
                "possible0": "work prioritization.",
                "possible1": "scheduling conflicts.",
                "possible2": "specific requests for assistance.",
                "possible3": "understanding the scope of demands.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "_id": "03-13",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "Those in the field of risk reduction need to become familiar with _____ in order to refer individuals to the proper source.",
                "refPage": "76",
                "possible0": "the scope of demands",
                "possible1": "time and effort reports",
                "possible2": "capabilities of a target audience",
                "possible3": "community agencies and organizations",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "_id": "03-14",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "Because fire and life safety educators are known to the community, they are in some ways:",
                "refPage": "78",
                "possible0": "always on call.",
                "possible1": "always on duty.",
                "possible2": "seen as evaluation professionals.",
                "possible3": "equal in rank to the service department.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "_id": "03-15",
                "chapterId": 3,
                "question": "What guideline should an FLSE follow to maintain a professional image and represent the department well?",
                "refPage": "78",
                "possible0": "Maintain a strict work-life balance.",
                "possible1": "Try to obtain the highest credentials possible.",
                "possible2": "Always speak and act as if the chief were watching.",
                "possible3": "Enlist the help of a professional speaking coach to improve public speaking abilities.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
